talkcorporation.com 2019-06-07

# Welcome to Talktelecom Corporation - Talkcorporation.com

| 

Talk Telecom Privacy Policy

Talk Telecom, Corp. ("Talk Telecom ") will not trade, sell, or disclose to any third party any form of subscriber identifiable information without the consent of the subscriber (except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case where failure to disclose information will lead to imminent harm to the subscriber or others). This includes information derived from registration, subscription, and use of Talk Telecom’s service. 

Use of Information

When you place an order through Talk Telecom, we use your personal information to process your order, and contact you with any questions via phone, email, or postal mail. 

Additionally, when you create an account with Talk Telecom and/or make a purchase with us, we will send you information regarding our promotions, products, and services. If you enter your information in response to any of our contests or promotions we will use your personal information (e-mail, phone number, or postal address) to send you information regarding our other promotions, products, services, and contests, unless you opt-out within your Account Preferences. On occasion, we might use your information to contact you to learn about your experiences with Talk Telecom and to conduct our own market research. 

Security

Talk Telecom is committed to keeping your personal information secure, and makes every effort to protect against its loss, misusage, or alteration. To protect your data, we use a variety of technologies and processes. Additionally, Talk Telecom provides only the information necessary to our outside companies, in order for them to fulfill their responsibilities. 

Talk Telecom protects & encrypts your order information using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology as it is transmitted over the Internet. If your browser or firewall does not support SSL, you will not be able to place an order online at Talk Telecom. If you are not able to access our secure server for any reason, our customer service team would be happy to assist you via phone. 

Communications

Talk Telecom will not read listen to or disclose to any third parties private e-mail, conversations, or other communications that are transmitted using Talk Telecom services, except as required to ensure proper operation of services or as otherwise authorized by law. 

Unlawful Activity

Talk Telecom may use subscriber identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of service, the network integrity, that otherwise violate Talk Telecom 's Service Agreements or activities that are or may be illegal. 

Account Information

The subscriber/customer is responsible for ensuring that the information on file with Talk Telecom is current and accurate. 

Children's Privacy Policy

Talk Telecom does not sell products or services for purchase or use by children. Talk Telecom does not knowingly solicit or collect subscriber identifiable information from children or teenagers under the age of eighteen. In addition, Talk Telecom will not knowingly link to any third party web site that solicits or collects subscriber identifiable information from minors. If you believe that a minor has disclosed personally identifiable information to Talk Telecom, please contact Talk Telecom at info@talkcorporation.com so that the information can be removed.

Talk Telecom Spam Policy 

When you provide Talk Telecom with your email address, expect to receive emails from us responding to your request or with information necessary to process your order. After placing your order with us, you will receive an email confirmation. 

Talk Telecom sends promotional emails, on occasion, to those individuals who have agreed to receive it. If you choose at any time to no longer receive email communications from Talk Telecom, simply unsubscribe by letting us know of that in each email communication provided by us.

Questions or Comments ?

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact Talk Telecom’s customer service team at CustomerCare@talkcorporation.com or 888.841.2235  
  
---
